RG 062:071, Town of Lebanon
Connecticut State Library
- Series 8. Tax Records, 1790-1928
  - Tax abstracts (Box 9)
    - South Society, 1899-1901 (Box 19)
    - Goshen Society, 1900-1902 (Box 19)
    - North Society, 1900-1903 (Box 19)
    - South Society, 1902-1906 (Box 19)
    - Goshen Society, 1903-1907 (Box 19)
    - North Society, 1904-1908 (Box 20)
    - Exeter Society, 1904-1908 (Box 20)
    - South Society, 1907-1908 (Box 20)
    - Goshen Society, 1908 (Box 20)
    - 1909-1914, 1 volume
    - 1915-1916, 1 volume
    - 1917, 1 volume
    - 1918-1920, 1 volume
    - 1921, 1 volume
    - 1922, 1 volume
    - 1923, 1 volume
    - 1924, 1 volume
    - 1925, 1 volume
    - 1926, 1 volume
    - 1927, 1 volume
    - 1928, 1 volume